Guide to the Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
- American Scientist Publication Files, 1950-2002; 1950 2002
  - Business, 1950-1997; 1950 1997
    - Advertising: Jandel Scientific, 1996 (Box 5.153, Folder 1)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulations Audit, 31 Dec. 1989 (Box 5.153, Folder 9)
    - Audit Report, Jul. 1992-Jun. 1993 (Box 5.132, Folder 7)
    - Billing, 1950-1955 (Box 5.153, Folder 10)
    - Board of Editors (1 of 2), 1970-1981 (Box 5.138, Folder 6)
    - Board of Editors (2 of 2), 1970-1981 (Box 5.138, Folder 7)
    - Budget, FY 1976-1985 (Box 5.137, Folder 3)
    - Budget, FY 1986-1989 (Box 5.137, Folder 4)
    - Business Manager, 1988 (Box 5.153, Folder 11)
    - Business Reply Envelopes, 1986 (Box 5.153, Folder 12)
    - Byrd Printing Company General Correspondence, 1977-1989 (Box 5.153, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence Regarding Subscriptions, 1990-1996 (Box 5.153, Folder 14)
    - General (Box 5.138, Folder 3)
    - Honorariums (Box 5.138, Folder 4)
    - Leads From Releases (Box 5.132, Folder 9)
    - Lists of Perspective Authors (Box 5.138, Folder 5)
    - Marketing Survey, 1971 (Box 5.153, Folder 15)
    - Masthead (Letters to Presidents), 1980-1989 (Box 5.153, Folder 16)
    - Meeting, 20 Jun. 1990 (Box 5.153, Folder 17)
    - Promotion and Subscriptions (Box 5.123, Folder 6)
    - Publisher's Statement, 1989-1997 (Box 5.137, Folder 2)
    - Publisher's Statement: January-June, 1990 (Box 5.131, Folder 3)
    - Publisher's Statement: January-June, 1991 (Box 5.131, Folder 6)
    - Publisher's Statement: January-June, 1992 (Box 5.132, Folder 2)
    - Publisher's Statement: January-June, 1993 (Box 5.132, Folder 5)
    - Publisher's Statement: July-December, 1990 (Box 5.131, Folder 4)
    - Publisher's Statement: July-December, 1992 (Box 5.132, Folder 3)
    - Publisher's Statement: July-December, 1993 (Box 5.132, Folder 6)
    - Publisher's Statement: July-December, 1991 (Box 5.131, Folder 7)
    - Quantum Ad (Box 5.132, Folder 8)
    - Reader Profile Study, 1988-1989 (Box 5.137, Folder 12)
    - Reader Profile Study, 1989 (Box 5.137, Folder 13)
    - Reader Profile Study, 1991 (Box 5.138, Folder 1)
    - Reader Profile Study, 1994 (Box 5.138, Folder 2)
    - Reader Service Card, Jun. 1988 (Box 5.153, Folder 18)
    - Reader Service Card, Apr. 1989 (Box 5.153, Folder 19)
    - Reader Surveys (Box 5.137, Folder 11)
    - Renewal/Invoice Records (Box 5.133, Folder 1)
    - Sales, 1989 (Box 5.137, Folder 5)
    - Sub Agency Advertisement, 1994 (Box 5.154, Folder 1)
  - Copyrights And Permissions, 1950-1986; 1950 1986
    - Jan. - Feb., 1978 (Box 5.128, Folder 5)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1978 (Box 5.128, Folder 6)
    - May - Jun., 1978 (Box 5.128, Folder 7)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1978 (Box 5.128, Folder 8)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1978 (Box 5.128, Folder 9)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1978 (Box 5.128, Folder 10)
    - Jan. - Feb., 1979 (Box 5.128, Folder 11)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1979 (Box 5.128, Folder 12)
    - May - Jun., 1979 (Box 5.128, Folder 13)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1979 (Box 5.128, Folder 14)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1979 (Box 5.128, Folder 15)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1979 (Box 5.128, Folder 16)
    - Jan. - Feb., 1980 (Box 5.129, Folder 1)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1980 (Box 5.129, Folder 2)
    - May - Jun., 1980 (Box 5.129, Folder 3)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1980 (Box 5.129, Folder 4)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1980 (Box 5.129, Folder 5)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1980 (Box 5.129, Folder 6)
    - Jan. - Feb., 1981 (Box 5.129, Folder 7)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1981 (Box 5.129, Folder 8)
    - May - Jun., 1981 (Box 5.129, Folder 9)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1981 (Box 5.129, Folder 10)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1981 (Box 5.129, Folder 11)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1981 (Box 5.129, Folder 12)
    - Jan. - Feb., 1982 (Box 5.129, Folder 13)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1982 (Box 5.129, Folder 14)
    - May - Jun., 1982 (Box 5.129, Folder 15)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1982 (Box 5.129, Folder 16)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1982 (Box 5.129, Folder 17)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1982 (Box 5.129, Folder 18)
    - Jan. - Feb., 1983 (Box 5.129, Folder 19)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1983 (Box 5.129, Folder 20)
    - May - Jun., 1983 (Box 5.129, Folder 21)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1983 (Box 5.129, Folder 22)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1983 (Box 5.129, Folder 23)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1983 (Box 5.129, Folder 24)
    - Jan. - Feb., 1984 (Box 5.129, Folder 25)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1984 (Box 5.129, Folder 26)
    - May - Jun., 1984 (Box 5.129, Folder 27)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1984 (Box 5.129, Folder 28)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1984 (Box 5.129, Folder 29)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1984 (Box 5.129, Folder 30)
    - Jan. - Feb., 1985 (Box 5.13, Folder 1)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1985 (Box 5.13, Folder 2)
    - May - Jun., 1985 (Box 5.13, Folder 3)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1985 (Box 5.13, Folder 4)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1985 (Box 5.13, Folder 5)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1985 (Box 5.13, Folder 6)
    - Jan. - Feb., 1986 (Box 5.13, Folder 7)
    - Mar. - Apr., 1986 (Box 5.13, Folder 8)
    - May - Jun., 1986 (Box 5.13, Folder 9)
    - Jul. - Aug., 1986 (Box 5.13, Folder 10)
    - Sep. - Oct., 1986 (Box 5.13, Folder 11)
    - Nov. - Dec., 1986 (Box 5.13, Folder 12)
    - Bulk Permissions (Box 5.131, Folder 1)
    - Bulk Permissions (Box 5.131, Folder 2)
    - Copyright Renewals, 1964-1977 (Box 5.13, Folder 15)
    - Forms (Box 5.137, Folder 1)
    - German, James (Box 5.127, Folder 5)
    - Princeton (Box 5.13, Folder 16)
    - Renewals Through, 1950 (Box 5.13, Folder 13)
    - Renewals, 1951-1979 (Box 5.13, Folder 14)
    - Reprints: A (Box 5.123, Folder 8)
    - Reprints: Ba (Box 5.124, Folder 1)
    - Reprints: Ba (Box 5.124, Folder 2)
    - Reprints: Bc-Be (Box 5.124, Folder 3)
    - Reprints: Bc-Be (Box 5.124, Folder 4)
    - Reprints: Berkowitz (Box 5.124, Folder 6)
    - Reprints: Bernstein (Box 5.124, Folder 5)
    - Reprints: Bf-Bl (Box 5.124, Folder 7)
    - Reprints: Bo-By (Box 5.124, Folder 9)
    - Reprints: Bo-By (Box 5.125, Folder 1)
    - Reprints: Bower (Box 5.124, Folder 8)
    - Reprints: C (Box 5.125, Folder 2)
    - Reprints: C (Box 5.125, Folder 3)
    - Reprints: C (Box 5.125, Folder 4)
    - Reprints: Cook, Mark (Box 5.125, Folder 5)
    - Reprints: Da-De (Box 5.125, Folder 6)
    - Reprints: Da-De (Box 5.125, Folder 7)
    - Reprints: Da-De (Box 5.125, Folder 8)
    - Reprints: Di-Dz (Box 5.126, Folder 1)
    - Reprints: Di-Dz (Box 5.126, Folder 2)
    - Reprints: E (Box 5.126, Folder 3)
    - Reprints: E (Box 5.126, Folder 4)
    - Reprints: E (Box 5.126, Folder 5)
    - Reprints: F (Box 5.126, Folder 6)
    - Reprints: Ga-Ge (Box 5.126, Folder 7)
    - Reprints: Ga-Ge (Box 5.127, Folder 1)
    - Reprints: Gi-Gz (Box 5.127, Folder 2)
    - Reprints: Gi-Gz (Box 5.127, Folder 3)
    - Reprints: Gi-Gz (Box 5.127, Folder 4)
    - Reprints: Ha-He (Box 5.127, Folder 7)
    - Reprints: Ha-He (Box 5.128, Folder 1)
    - Reprints: Ha-He (Box 5.128, Folder 2)
    - Reprints: Harlow (Box 5.127, Folder 6)
    - Reprints: Hi-Hy (Box 5.128, Folder 3)
    - Reprints: Hi-Hy (Box 5.128, Folder 4)
  - General
    - Annual Index, Nov. 1989 (Box 5.154, Folder 2)
    - Awards: ASAE (American Society of Association Executives) (Box 5.137, Folder 7)
    - Awards: ASME (American Society of Magazine Editors) (Box 5.137, Folder 6)
    - Awards: Ozzie, 1989 (Box 5.137, Folder 8)
    - Awards: SNAP (Society of National Association Publications), 1986 (Box 5.137, Folder 9)
    - Awards: SNAP, 1988 (Box 5.137, Folder 10)
    - Biology: Checklists (Box 5.133, Folder 8)
    - Biology: History (Box 5.133, Folder 11)
    - Biology: Ideas (Box 5.133, Folder 13)
    - Biology: Information (Box 5.133, Folder 7)
    - Biology: L. Byrd (Box 5.133, Folder 2)
    - Biology: Letters To The Editor (Box 5.133, Folder 4)
    - Biology: Manuscripts To Be Invited (Box 5.133, Folder 6)
    - Biology: Manuscripts (Box 5.133, Folder 10)
    - Biology: Nancy Knowlton (Box 5.133, Folder 3)
    - Biology: Rick Harrison (Box 5.133, Folder 9)
    - Biology: Sports (Box 5.133, Folder 5)
    - Biology: Word Process (Box 5.133, Folder 12)
    - Brochure, 1972-1973 (Box 5.154, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Lecturers, 1985-1986 (Oversizelegalbox 5.136, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Lecturers, 1985-1986 (Oversizelegalbox 5.136, Folder 5)
    - Cover, May - Jun. 1989 (Box 5.154, Folder 4)
    - Cumulative Index, undated (Box 5.154, Folder 5)
    - Direction, 1981 (Box 5.154, Folder 6)
    - Edinburgh International Science Festival, 1994 (Box 5.154, Folder 7)
    - Environmental (Box 5.133, Folder 16)
    - General Information of All Aspects of Publishing, undated (Box 5.154, Folder 8)
    - Lecturers, 1987-1988 (Oversizelegalbox 5.136, Folder 6)
    - Lecturers, 1987-1988 (Oversizelegalbox 5.136, Folder 7)
    - Lecturers, 1987-1988 (Oversizelegalbox 5.136, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts Expected (Box 5.133, Folder 14)
    - Master Forms, undated (Box 5.154, Folder 9)
    - McKeeman/Grinter Chinese Scientists, 1979 (Box 5.154, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5.133, Folder 15)
    - National Lecturers, 1988 (Oversizelegalbox 5.135, Folder 1)
    - National Lecturers, 1988 (Oversizelegalbox 5.135, Folder 2)
    - National Lecturers, 1989 (Oversizelegalbox 5.135, Folder 3)
    - National Lecturers, 1989 (Oversizelegalbox 5.135, Folder 4)
    - National Lecturers, 1990 (Oversizelegalbox 5.135, Folder 5)
    - National Lecturers, 1984 (Oversizelegalbox 5.134, Folder 1)
    - National Lecturers, 1984 (Oversizelegalbox 5.134, Folder 2)
    - National Lecturers, 1985 (Oversizelegalbox 5.134, Folder 3)
    - National Lecturers, 1985 (Oversizelegalbox 5.134, Folder 4)
    - National Lecturers, 1985 (Oversizelegalbox 5.134, Folder 5)
    - O'Brien (Oversizelegalbox 5.136, Folder 1)
    - O'Brien (Oversizelegalbox 5.136, Folder 2)
    - O'Brien (Oversizelegalbox 5.136, Folder 3)
    - Paging And Second Color (Box 5.133, Folder 18)
    - Personnel, 1981 (Box 5.154, Folder 11)
    - Photographs: Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 5.154, Folder 12)
    - Photographs: Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 5.154, Folder 14)
    - Photographs: Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 5.155, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 5.155, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 5.154, Folder 13)
    - Photographs: Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 5.155, Folder 3)
    - Photographs: Lecturers/Officers (Box 5.155, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: Lecturers/Officers (Box 5.155, Folder 5)
    - Photographs: Lecturers/Officers (Box 5.155, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Lecturers/Officers (Box 5.155, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: Lecturers/Officers (Box 5.155, Folder 8)
    - Photographs: Lecturers/Officers (Box 5.155, Folder 9)
    - Photographs: Lecturers/Officers (Box 5.155, Folder 10)
    - Photographs: Sigma Xi Building (Box 5.156, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Smithsonian Employees (Box 5.156, Folder 2)
    - Policy Statement, 1969-1980 (Box 5.156, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings (Box 5.138, Folder 8)
    - Printing (Box 5.133, Folder 17)
    - Publisher, 1952-1954 (Box 5.156, Folder 4)
    - Publisher, 1969-1973 (Box 5.156, Folder 5)
    - Publisher, 1974-1986 (Box 5.156, Folder 6)
    - Reader Profile Study, 1987-1988 (Box 5.156, Folder 7)
    - Relevant Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 5.156, Folder 8)
    - Scrapbook, 1978-1979 (Oversizeflatbox 5.157)
    - Statistics, 1951-1953 (Box 5.156, Folder 9)
- Subject Files, 1951-2003; 1951 2003; 22 linear feet
  This series contains files that do not belong to any of the previous series and subseries. Files in this series are arranged alphabetically, then chronologically therein.
  - "A New Agenda For Science": General, 1983-1987 (Box 6.022, Folder 1)
  - "A New Agenda For Science": General, 1986 (Box 6.022, Folder 6)
  - "A New Agenda For Science": Pamphlet, 1987 (Box 6.022, Folder 4)
  - "A New Agenda For Science": Pamphlets, 1986 (Box 6.022, Folder 3)
  - "A New Agenda For Science": Preliminary Report, 1986 (Box 6.022, Folder 2)
  - "A New Agenda For Science": Project Packet, 1985 (Box 6.022, Folder 5)
  - A Provisional White Paper on University Objectives: University of Toronto, 1994 (Box 6.024, Folder 11)
  - Acadme, 1986-1987 (Box 6.001, Folder 1)
  - Agency for International Development, 1982-1988 (Box 6.001, Folder 2)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1988-1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 4)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science: Consortium of Affiliates for International Programs, 15 Sep. 1995 (Box 6.001, Folder 5)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science: Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 6.001, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Administrators, 1985 (Box 6.001, Folder 6)
  - American Chemical Society, 1988 (Box 6.001, Folder 7)
  - American Geophysical Union Proposal, 1997 (Box 6.004, Folder 10)
  - American Heritage, 1985-1992 (Box 6.001, Folder 8)
  - American Men and Women of Science, 1979-1988 (Box 6.001, Folder 10)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1983 (Box 6.001, Folder 11)
  - American Society for Photobiology, 1983-1990 (Box 6.001, Folder 12)
  - American-Lebanon Private Sector Cooperation, 1982 (Box 6.001, Folder 9)
  - Animal Rights Meeting, 22 Jul. 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 13)
  - Animals in Research: Chapter Responses Received Jan. 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 14)
  - Animals in Research: Chapter Responses Received Feb. 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 15)
  - Animals in Research: Chapter Responses Received 1-11 Mar. 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 16)
  - Animals in Research: Chapter Responses Received 12-28 Mar. 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 17)
  - Animals in Research: Chapter Responses Received Apr. - Jul. 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 18)
  - Animals in Research: Chapter Responses Unknown Date of Receipt (Box 6.001, Folder 19)
  - Animals in Research: Correspondence: Outside Sigma Xi, 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 20)
  - Animals in Research: Correspondence: Rutgers University Chapter, 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 21)
  - Animals in Research: Correspondence: Statement, 1991 (Box 6.001, Folder 22)
  - Animals in Research: Cosmetic Testing, 1991-1992 (Box 6.001, Folder 23)
  - Animals in Research: General, 1990 (Box 6.002, Folder 1)
  - Animals in Research: Grant Requests, 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 2)
  - Animals in Research: Grant Research, 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 3)
  - Animals in Research: January Article: Member Responses Received Jan. 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 4)
  - Animals in Research: January Article: Member Responses Received 1-6 Feb. 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 5)
  - Animals in Research: January Article: Member Responses Received 7-28 Feb. 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 6)
  - Animals in Research: January Article: Member Responses Received Mar. - Jul. 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 7)
  - Animals in Research: January Article: Members Responses Unknown Date of Receipt (Box 6.002, Folder 8)
  - Animals in Research: June Article: Responses, 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 9)
  - Animals in Research: Meeting: Correspondence: Participant Follow-up, 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 11)
  - Animals in Research: Meeting: Correspondence: Potential Participants, 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 10)
  - Animals in Research: Meeting: Jerry Eberhart's Notes, 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 13)
  - Animals in Research: Meeting: Planning, 1990-1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 12)
  - Animals in Research: Membership Survey, 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 14)
  - Animals in Research: Opposed Views, 1991 (Box 6.002, Folder 15)
  - Animals in Research: Request to Chapters and Clubs, 1990 (Box 6.002, Folder 16)
  - Animals in Research: Resource List, May 1992 (Box 6.002, Folder 17)
  - Animals in Research: Resource List, 1992 (Box 6.003, Folder 1)
  - Animals in Research: Resource List and Statement Requests, 1992 (Box 6.003, Folder 2)
  - Animals in Research: Response Tallies, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 14)
  - Animals in Research: Responses to Summary of Responses, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 16)
  - Animals in Research: Statement on the Use of Animals in Research, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 11)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Articles, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 13)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Correspondence: Possible Reviewers, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 12)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Pre-First Draft, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 3)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: First Draft: Comments, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 4)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Second Draft: Comments, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 5)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Third Draft and Fax Cover Letters, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 6)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Third Draft: Comments, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 7)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Fourth Draft: Comments, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 8)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Fifth Draft and Fax Cover Sheets, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 9)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Fifth Draft: Comments, 1991 (Box 6.003, Folder 10)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Responses in Agreement, 1992 (Box 6.003, Folder 17)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Responses in Disagreement, 1992 (Box 6.003, Folder 18)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Responses: Resignations, A-K (Box 6.003, Folder 19)
  - Animals in Research: Statement: Responses: Resignations, L-Z, 1992 (Box 6.003, Folder 20)
  - Animals in Research: Summary of Responses, 1990 (Box 6.003, Folder 15)
  - Animals in Research: University of Iowa Chapter, 1991 (Box 6.004, Folder 1)
  - Animals in Research: Workshop and Background Information, 1990 (Box 6.004, Folder 2)
  - Annual Review Publications, 1991-1992 (Box 6.004, Folder 3)
  - Archives, 1986-1987 (Box 6.004, Folder 6)
  - ARCO Grant, 1991 (Box 6.004, Folder 4)
  - Association for College Honor Societies, 1982-1985 (Box 6.004, Folder 5)
  - Audio and Video Available from Sigma Xi, 1984-1989 (Box 6.004, Folder 7)
  - Awards, 1992-1994 (Box 6.004, Folder 8)
  - Awards: Seal Designs, 1995 (Box 6.004, Folder 9)
  - Balfour Company, 1963-1971 (Box 6.004, Folder 11)
  - Bank of Delaware, 1986-1991 (Box 6.004, Folder 12)
  - Bates College: Ladd Program, 1987-1988 (Box 6.004, Folder 13)
  - Beazley Company, 1982-1988 (Box 6.004, Folder 14)
  - Beirut, 1978-1983 (Box 6.004, Folder 15)
  - Bequest Inquiries, 1972-1984 (Box 6.004, Folder 16)
  - Bequest Notifications, 1974-1984 (Box 6.004, Folder 17)
  - Billing Inquiries, 1967 (Box 6.004, Folder 18)
  - Billing Inquiries, 1967 (Box 6.005, Folder 1)
  - Black Scientists, 1990 (Box 6.013, Folder 16)
  - Bounty Hunter Project, 1983-1984 (Box 6.005, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1983 (Box 6.005, Folder 3)
  - Brode, Wallace: Speech, 1972 (Box 6.013, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1986 (Box 6.005, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Corporation: Report of the Committee on Science, Technology, and Government, Oct. 1992 (Box 6.005, Folder 5)
  - Cassidy, Harold G.: Photo and Paper, undated (Box 6.005, Folder 6)
  - Centennial History of Sigma Xi, 1986 (Box 6.005, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Poster, 1986 (Oversizebox 6.04, Folder 1)
  - Certificate: Hundredth Anniversary, 1986 (Oversizeflatbox 7.006, Folder 1)
  - Certificate: State University of Ghent, Belgium to Sigma Xi, in Honor of Toxicology Research, 1976 (Oversizeflatbox 7.006, Folder 2)
  - Citizens for Ocean Law, 1981-1982 (Box 6.005, Folder 8)
  - Companion's Club Dinner, 20 Apr. 1991 (Box 6.005, Folder 9)
  - Computing, 1970-1976 (Box 6.005, Folder 10)
  - Computing, 1977-1982, 1985 (Box 6.005, Folder 11)
  - Computing: Process, 1975-1983 (Box 6.005, Folder 12)
  - Congressional Science Fellows, 1985 (Box 6.005, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering, 1986-1988 (Box 6.005, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut Communications, 1979-1982 (Box 6.005, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Public Radio, 1986 (Box 6.005, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Events: Centennial, 1982-1986 (Box 6.006, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: A Miscellaneous, 1973-1985 (Box 6.006, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: A Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 6.006, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Anderson, V. Elving, 1971-1986 (Box 6.006, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Apple, Martin, 1988 (Box 6.006, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: B Miscellaneous, 1972-1982 (Box 6.006, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: B Miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box 6.006, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: B Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 6.006, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Barber, Mary Lee, 1978-1979 (Box 6.006, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Bender, Dr. Harvey, 1981-1988 (Box 6.006, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Bixby, Herbert, 1980 (Box 6.006, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Branscomb, Lewis, 1983-1985 (Box 6.006, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Branscomb, Lewis, 1986 (Box 6.006, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Bromley, D. Allan, 1988 (Box 6.006, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Burrill, Melinda, 1985-1986 (Box 6.006, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: C Miscellaneous, 1978-1985 (Box 6.006, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: C Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 6.006, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Carson, Gordon B., 1978-1982 (Box 6.007, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Carson, Gordon B., 1983-1985 (Box 6.007, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Carson, Gordon B., 1986-1988 (Box 6.007, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Cassidy, Harold G., 1975-1977 (Box 6.007, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Cassidy, Harold G., 22 Dec. 1977 (Box 6.007, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Chiu, Arthur, 1980-1985 (Box 6.007, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Croxton, Frank, 1967- Feb. 1971 (Box 6.007, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Croxton, Frank, 1971 (Box 6.007, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Croxton, Frank, 1972 (Box 6.007, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Croxton, Frank, 1973-1980 (Box 6.007, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: D Miscellaneous, 1980-1988 (Box 6.008, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Daniels, Farrington, 1967-1972 (Box 6.008, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Douple, Evan, 1981-1985 (Box 6.008, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: E Miscellaneous, 1972-1988 (Box 6.008, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: F Miscellaneous, 1978-1988 (Box 6.008, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Faber, M. Patricia, 1982-1984 (Box 6.008, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Faber, M. Patricia, 1984-1988 (Box 6.008, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Faull, Anna and J. Horace, 1981-1984 (Box 6.008, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: G Miscellaneous, 1973-1983 (Box 6.008, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: G Miscellaneous, 1984-1987 (Box 6.008, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Geller, Art, 1986-1988 (Box 6.008, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Golding, Brage, 1980 (Box 6.008, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Goodgame, Thomas, 1977 (Box 6.008, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Grinter, Linton E., 1974-1975 (Box 6.008, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Grinter, Linton E., 1975-1985 (Box 6.008, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: H Miscellaneous, 1979-1986 (Box 6.008, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: H Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 6.008, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Halle, Mark, 1981-1984 (Box 6.008, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Hammond, Allen L., 1987 (Box 6.008, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Hare, F. Kenneth, 1982-1987 (Box 6.009, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Haskins, Caryl P., 1966-1980 (Box 6.009, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Haskins, Caryl P., 1966-1980 (Box 6.009, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: I Miscellaneous, 1979-1987 (Box 6.009, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: J Miscellaneous, 1978-1988 (Box 6.009, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: K Miscellaneous, 1979-1988 (Box 6.009, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Knoble, Susan, 1986 (Box 6.009, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Kranzberg, Melvin, 1980-1981 (Box 6.009, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Kranzberg, Melvin, 1982-1985 (Box 6.009, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Kranzberg, Melvin, 1986-1988 (Box 6.009, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Kuney, Joseph, 1982-1986 (Box 6.009, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Kushner, Lawrence, 1975-1988 (Box 6.009, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: L Miscellaneous, 1978-1988 (Box 6.009, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: L Miscellaneous, 1980-1988 (Box 6.009, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Landfred, Steven, 1981 (Box 6.009, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Lane, Neal, 1993-1996 (Box 6.039, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: M Miscellaneous, 1971-1983 (Box 6.009, Folder 16)